const Data = [
  {
    "id": "1",
    "Question": "What does SCSS stand for?",
    "answers": ["Semantic Cascading Style Sheets", "Special Cascading Style Sheets", "Sassy Cascading Style Sheets"],
    "correctAnswer": "Sassy Cascading Style Sheets"
  },
  {
    "id": "2",
    "Question": "What is SCSS?",
    "answers": ["a CSS preprocessor", "a compiler", "a library"],
    "correctAnswer": "a CSS preprocessor"
  },
  {
    "id": "3",
    "Question": "What is a preprocessor?",
    "answers": ["a tool which will process code and compile it to a new format", 
      "converts source code into something that can run on a computer", 
      "a text-only way of browsing and interacting with your computer"],
    "correctAnswer": "a tool which will process code and compile it to a new format"
  },
  {
    "id": "4",
    "Question": "What does SASS stand for?",
    "answers": ["Syntactically Awesome Style Sheets", "Super Awesome Style Sheets", "Semantically Awesome Style Sheets"],
    "correctAnswer": "Syntactically Awesome Style Sheets"
  },
  {
    "id": "5",
    "Question": "What is another example of a preprocessor?",
    "answers": ["Styled", "SCAT", "Less"],
    "correctAnswer": "Less"
  },
  {
    "id": "6",
    "Question": "What is one reason SCSS is preferred over SASS?",
    "answers": ["syntax is much easier to write", "It is newer", "SASS is difficult to read"],
    "correctAnswer": "syntax is much easier to write"
  },
  {
    "id": "7",
    "Question": "What is the correct syntax for defining a variable in SCSS?",
    "answers": ["$favorite-color: purple", "@favorite-color: purple", "&favorite-color: purple"],
    "correctAnswer": "$favorite-color: purple"
  },
  {
    "id": "8",
    "Question": "Where can SCSS variables be used?",
    "answers": ["anywhere in any style sheet", "anywhere in SCSS style sheets", "anywhere in SASS style sheets"],
    "correctAnswer": "anywhere in SCSS style sheets"
  },
  {
    "id": "9",
    "Question": "What is an advantage of using variables in SCSS?",
    "answers": ["allows for more creativity", "makes confusing properties easier to read", "saves from typing out especially long, specific styles"],
    "correctAnswer": "saves from typing out especially long, specific styles"
  },
  {
    "id": "10",
    "Question": "Does regular CSS accept variables?",
    "answers": ["yes", "no", "only in special circumstances"],
    "correctAnswer": "Yes"
  },
  {
    "id": "11",
    "Question": "What is nesting in SCSS?",
    "answers": ["practice of combining multiple variables into one", 
      "represents the relationships between HTML elements in CSS", 
      "a group of CSS declarations to be reused throughout the site"],
    "correctAnswer": "represents the relationships between HTML elements in CSS"
  },
  {
    "id": "12",
    "Question": "Why is too much nesting a problem?",
    "answers": ["creates overly specific CSS",
    "makes the Sass file too difficult to read",
    "takes too long to compile"],
    "correctAnswer": "creates overly specific CSS"
  },
  {
    "id": "13",
    "Question": "What is the correct syntax for nesting in SCSS?", //needs images
    "answers": ["<image>", "<image2>", "<image3>"],
    "correctAnswer": "<image>"
  },
  {
    "id": "14",
    "Question": "Sass is a superset language â€” what does that mean?",
    "answers": ["everything that works in CSS will still work in Sass or SCSS", 
    "it combines CSS and Javascript", 
    "Sass uses variables to create supersets"],
    "correctAnswer": "everything that works in CSS will still work in Sass or SCSS"
  },
  {
    "id": "15",
    "Question": "<image> This code would output to:", //nesting example
    "answers": ["<image>", "<image2>", "<image3>"],
    "correctAnswer": "<image>"
  },
  {
    "id": "16",
    "Question": "<image> This code provides an example of:", //nesting example
    "answers": ["nesting", "extend", "mixins"],
    "correctAnswer": "nesting"
  },
  {
    "id": "17",
    "Question": "What is the advantage of the @import directive?",
    "answers": ["", 
    "", 
    "compiles stylesheets so only one HTTP request is made to the server"],
    "correctAnswer": "compiles stylesheets so only one HTTP request is made to the server"
  },
  {
    "id": "18",
    "Question": "Where does the @import directive get used and why?",
    "answers": ["only once at the top of the index.scss file", 
      "in every .scss file to import all styles", 
      "in index.scss for each individual SCSS files"],
    "correctAnswer": "in index.scss for each individual SCSS files"
  },
  {
    "id": "19",
    "Question": "How should Sass files be named?",
    "answers": ["doctorSass.scss", "_doctorSass.scss", "doctorSass.css"],
    "correctAnswer": "doctorSass.scss"
  },
  {
    "id": "20",
    "Question": "What is a partial Sass file?",
    "answers": ["snippets of CSS to be included in other CSS files", 
      "Sass file without anything imported into it", 
      "Sass file with poor/incomplete syntax"],
    "correctAnswer": "snippets of CSS to be included in other CSS files"
  },
  {
    "id": "21",
    "Question": "What is a potential use case of a partial Sass file?",
    "answers": ["a file with all the defined Sass variables", 
      "file with all the imported partial Sass files", 
      "placeholder for styles that may not end up being used"],
    "correctAnswer": "a file with all the defined Sass variables"
  },
  {
    "id": "22",
    "Question": "How should a partial Sass file be named?",
    "answers": ["doctorSass.scss", "doctorSass.css", "_doctorSass.scss"],
    "correctAnswer": "_doctorSass.scss"
  },
  {
    "id": "23",
    "Question": "What is a Sass mixin?",
    "answers": ["a mix of the two given colors based on the weight percentage provided", 
      "a group of CSS declarations to be reused throughout the site", 
      "a delicious option at ColdStone creamery"],
    "correctAnswer": "a group of CSS declarations to be reused throughout the site"
  },
  {
    "id": "24",
    "Question": "What is the proper way to define a Sass mixin?",
    "answers": ["@mixin mixinName(arguments) { style }", "@mixinName(arguments) { style }", "@mixin mixinName{ style }"],
    "correctAnswer": "@mixin mixinName(arguments) { style }"
  },
  {
    "id": "25",
    "Question": "What is especially sassy feature of mixins?",
    "answers": ["they accept arguments which can be used to pass values", 
      "inherits properties from other selectors", 
      "they can be used in javascript"],
    "correctAnswer": "they accept arguments which can be used to pass values"
  },
  {
    "id": "26",
    "Question": "How is a Sass mixin called once it has been defined?",
    "answers": ["@include mixinName(potentialArguments)", "@mixinName()", "@mixinName(potentialArguments)"],
    "correctAnswer": "@include mixinName(potentialArguments)"
  },
  {
    "id": "27",
    "Question": "What does the @extend directive do in Sass?",
    "answers": ["inherits properties from other selectors", 
      "extends partial Sass files", 
      "imports Sass color functions"],
    "correctAnswer": "inherits properties from other selectors"
  },
  {
    "id": "28",
    "Question": "What is the proper syntax for using @extend?", //needs images
    "answers": ["<image>", "<image2>", "<image3>"],
    "correctAnswer": "<image>"
  },
  {
    "id": "29",
    "Question": "What are color functions?",
    "answers": ["functions provided by Sass to allow color manipulation", 
      "a tool for selecting color schemes for an entire project", 
      "a wider variety of color selectors provided in Sass"],
    "correctAnswer": "functions provided by Sass to allow color manipulation"
  },
  {
    "id": "30",
    "Question": "What does color() accept as an argument?",
    "answers": ["a single color", 
      "two colors and the weight percentage", 
      "two colors"],
    "correctAnswer": "a single color"
  },
  {
    "id": "31",
    "Question": "What does color() return?",
    "answers": ["the 180-degree complement of the color passed through as an argument", 
      "the hex value of that color", 
      "a mix of the two given colors based on the weight percentage provided"],
    "correctAnswer": "the 180-degree complement of the color passed through as an argument"
  },
  {
    "id": "32",
    "Question": "What does mix() accept as an argument?",
    "answers": ["two colors and a percentage", "two colors", "two colors and a number"],
    "correctAnswer": "two colors and the weight percentage"
  },
  {
    "id": "33",
    "Question": "What does mix() return?",
    "answers": ["the 180-degree complement of the color passed through as an argument", 
      "a mix of the two given colors based on the weight percentage provided", 
      ""],
    "correctAnswer": "a mix of the two given colors based on the weight percentage provided"
  },
  {
    "id": "34",
    "Question": "Using mix(purple, gold, 100%), which color will be represented?",
    "answers": ["100% purple", "100% gold", "a 100% mix"],
    "correctAnswer": "100% purple"
  },
  {
    "id": "35",
    "Question": "What arguments does lighten() accept?",
    "answers": ["one color and a number", "one color and a percentage", "two colors and a percentage"],
    "correctAnswer": "one color and a percentage"
  },
  {
    "id": "36",
    "Question": "What does darken(color, amount) return?",
    "answers": ["the given color darkened by the percentage given", 
      "the given color desaturated by the percentage given", 
      "the given color darkened by the pixels given"],
    "correctAnswer": "the given color darkened by the percentage given"
  },
  {
    "id": "37",
    "Question": "What does desaturate(color, amount) return?",
    "answers": ["the given color desaturated by the percentage given", 
      "the given color darkened by the percentage given", 
      "the given color desaturated"],
    "correctAnswer": "the given color desaturated by the percentage given"
  },
  {
    "id": "38",
    "Question": "What arguments does saturate() accept?",
    "answers": ["two colors and a number", "one color and a percentage", "one color and a number"],
    "correctAnswer": "one color and a percentage"
  },
  {
    "id": "39",
    "Question": "How is the & symbol used in Sass?",
    "answers": ["& is converted to the name of the parent element when nesting", 
      "& is used to link variables together", 
      "& is not used in Sass and will throw an error"],
    "correctAnswer": "& is converted to the name of the parent element when nesting"
  },
  {
    "id": "40",
    "Question": "Can arithmetic operators be used in Sass?",
    "answers": ["Yes", "No", "Yes, but why would you?"],
    "correctAnswer": "Yes, but why would you?"
  },
  {
    "id": "41",
    "Question": "What does the @if directive do?",
    "answers": ["@if is not a Sass directive", 
      "sets style based on a condition", 
      "repeats CSS definitions multiple times in a row"],
    "correctAnswer": "sets style based on a condition"
  },
  {
    "id": "42",
    "Question": "What does the @for directive do",
    "answers": ["repeats CSS definitions multiple times in a row", 
      "sets style based on a condition", 
      "@for is not a Sass directive"],
    "correctAnswer": "repeats CSS definitions multiple times in a row"
  },
  {
    "id": "43",
    "Question": "How is the * symbol used in Sass?",
    "answers": ["* is converted to the name of the parent element when nesting",
      "* is used to link variables together",
      "* is not used in Sass and will throw an error"],
    "correctAnswer": "* is not used in Sass and will throw an error"
  },
  {
    "id": "44",
    "Question": "What does the @onceler directive do",
    "answers": ["repeats CSS definitions multiple times in a row",
      "sets style based on a condition",
      "@onceler is not a Sass directive"],
    "correctAnswer": "repeats CSS definitions multiple times in a row"
  }
]

export default Data;